Hello Hello everyone, this is Yamagio's little class.
Today, I will give you a few MD tips.
It will be more efficient when you are making clothes, and you can finish it faster.
First of all, for example, when we are making clothes,
the clothes are accidentally moved to a place that we can't see from our perspective.
What should we do at this time?
Do we have to keep moving to a place that we can see?
In fact, you don't have to keep looking.
In fact, at this time, we only need to right-click on the blank area and click on the zoom to the whole scene.
This clothes will come back.
Similarly, in 2D, now we go back to the operation interface in 2D.
For example, if we want to find the version,
it is also so accidentally, for example, like this, accidentally moved to a place that we can't see.
At this time, we still need to right-click and click on the zoom to the whole scene.
Then our version will come back.
The second little trick,
is to wait for it to move.
For example, we now want to change the shape of this version.
Then how do we enter a precise value?
First of all, we move it like this.
Then at this time, we click on the right arrow of the mouse.
Then we can enter, for example, the distance we want.
For example, 8 centimeters.
Okay, that's fine.
Then the other side is also possible.
We are now moving to the left.
Then click on the right arrow, 8 centimeters.
Then we can move the value here.
Okay, now let's come to our third md little trick,
which is called the value copy and the value paste.
For example, when we usually make a belt,
it will have some holes like this.
Or when making some clothes,
there will also be some internal patterns of the value.
Then how to make it at this time?
Do we have to keep drawing one inside,
and then keep pressing ctrl-c, ctrl-v to paste it like this?
Then how to make it at this time?
Do we have to keep pressing ctrl-c, ctrl-v to paste it like this?
In fact, it doesn't have to be so troublesome.
At this time, we only need to draw an internal pattern here.
Then I move it to this side to make it easier to see.
Then we only need to ctrl-c, ctrl-v.
If ctrl-v is to be moved to the side,
then we right-click and click on the scale.
The scale is based on the distance you want.
Just look at the color you want.
Then at this time, we will decide the number ourselves.
Then it's good.
Then these are all internal patterns of some equations.
Then at this time, we just click on it to convert it to a hole.
Then the hole is dug.
Okay, this episode of Yamaha's little class is over.
In the next episode, I will continue to share some MD little skills.